Neil P. Speirs Collection of U.S. Railroad Retirement Board Member Photographs 6215 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Neil P. Speirs Collection of U.S Railroad Retirement Board Member Photographs
1952-1973
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Speirs, Neil P.
U.S. Railroad Retirement Board
6215 P
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Photographs.
This collection contains the photographs of Neil P. Speirs, former president of the Switchmen's Union of North America [SUNA], assistant president of the United Transportation Union [UTU], and labor member of the U.S. Railroad Retirement Board.
7993996
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
E. Parker, March 22, 2013
EAD encoding:
Elizabeth Parker, December 07, 2017
Biographical / Historical
Neil P. Speirs was born in Alberta, Canada, on December 25, 1912 and moved to the United States with his parents in 1919. He became a naturalized citizen in 1942. Mr. Speirs graduated from the University of Idaho in 1934, having majored in business and education.
Mr. Speirs began his railroad career with Southern Pacific Railroad, working in the railroad's train yards. He was first elected to the local Grievance Committee of Adjustment for the Switchmen's Union of North America [SUNA], Local 98 (San Francisco, CA) in 1950. In 1952, he was elected as a full-time officer, serving as chairman of the General Grievance Committee of Adjustment, Southern Pacific Railroad [SP]. Mr. Speirs served in this capacity until 1955, when he was elected to serve as SUNA International Vice-President. In 1959, he was elected to be President of SUNA and served as President until January 1, 1969.
On January 1, 1969 SUNA, along with the Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen, the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen formed the United Transportation Union [UTU]. Upon the merger, Mr. Speirs became Assistant President of UTU.
In 1969, President Richard Nixon appointed Mr. Speirs as the Labor Member of the Railroad Retirement Board. In 1974, President Gerald Ford re-appointed him to that position. He retired from the Railroad Retirement Board in 1977, but served on the Arbitration Panel of the National Mediation Board on a part-time basis until 1978.
Scope and Contents
Inclusive date range: 1952-1973, undated
Bulk dates: 1960-1968
This collection consists of a photograph scrapbook and loose photographs collected by Neil P. Speirs. The photographs document his various activities as president of SUNA, assistant president of the UTU, labor member of the Railroad Retirement Board, and other activities in which he participated in the course of his work in organized labor. Mr. Speirs' personal scrapbook contains annotation identifying the people in the photographs as well as where and when they were taken. Of note in this album are four photographs of Eleanor Roosevelt at the AFL-CIO convention in Miami Beach, Florida. Many of the pictures in the scrapbook are duplicated in the loose pictures in this collection. Other notable photographs picture Mr. Speirs with President Lyndon B. Johnson in 1965, when the president signed an act authorizing investigation into the use of high-speed ground transportation systems. Many of the photographs are from the various meeting and conventions that preceded the creation of the UTU in 1969. There are numerous picture of Mr. Speirs with the other three union presidents that united to form the UTU. The men are Charles Luna, president of the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, H. E. Gilbert, the president of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Engineers, and C. F. Lane, the president of the Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen. Many of the photographs of these four men may be found in the UTU pamphlets in Collection 6215, ""=Neil P. Speirs Collection of U.S. Railroad Retirement Board Member Files, 1963-1994." Finally, there are many pictures of the participants from the labor group who participated in the U. S. President's Railroad Commission in 1960.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6215 MB: Neil P. Speirs Collection of U.S. Railroad Retirement Board Memorabilia 6215: Neil P. Speirs Collection of U.S. Railroad Retirement Board Member Files 5034: Switchmen's Union of North America Records 5034 MB: Switchmen's Union of North America Memorabilia 5034 P: Switchmen's Union of North America Photographs 5084: Switchmen's Union of North America Additional Records 5405 mf: Switchmen's Union of North America Constitutions on Microfilm 5406 mf: Switchmen's Union of North America Arbitration on Microfilm 5447: Switchmen's Union of North America Additional Unification Minutes and Convention Proceedings 5556: Switchmen's Union of North America Additional Records 5139: UTU Records 5139 AV: UTU Audio-Visual Material 5139 MB: UTU Memorabilia 5139 P: UTU Photographs 5003: U.S. President's Railroad Commission Records 5003 P: U.S. President's Railroad Commission Photographs
Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions; Speirs, Neil P.; Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962; Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973; Mitchell, James Paul, 1900-1961; Lyons, A. E.; Luna, Charles, 1906-; Gilbert, H. E.; Lane, C. F.; Switchmen's Union of North America; United Transportation Union; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen; Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen; Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen; U.S. Railroad Retirement Board; U.S. President's Railroad Commission, 1960; AFL-CIO; United States. Railroad Retirement Board--Photographs
7993996
- Personal scrapbook of SUNA events and other labor events, 1955-1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  39 photographs (photo album, kept together). Pages are laminated, photographs have captions identifying people in photographs. Includes photos of U.S. President's Commission on Railroads, photos of Eleanor Roosevelt at AFL-CIO convention, and photos of various SUNA events.
  - Item 1: Page 1, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    : Labor chiefs, Presidential Railroad Commission, 1960. Left to right; myself, H.E. Gilbert (President of BLF&E), A.F. Zimmerman, (Assistant Grand Chief, BLE), J.A. Paddock (President of ORC&B), W.P. Kennedy (President of BRT), Secretary of Labor James P. Mitchell. The signing of the agreement to form a presidential Commission to settle work rules and practices disputes in the railroad industry.
    Format: black and white photograph.
  - Item 2: Page 2, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Carriers, Presidential railroad Commission signing, 1960. Left to right seated; Secretary of Labor James P. Mitchell, G.W. Knight (Director, Labor relations, Pennsylvania railroad), T. Short (Chairman, Committee on Labor Relations, the Association of Western Railways). Standing; Under-Secretary of Labor James T. O'Connell, L.B. Fee, (Vice-president, Seaboard Air Line Railroad), E.H. Hallmann, (Director of Personnel, Illinois Central Railroad Company).
  - Item 3: Page 3, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    (Left) David McDonald (left), President of the Steelworkers. (Middle) George Meany, President of the AFL-CIO. (Right) Schlitzer, Secretary-Treasurer of the AFL-CIO. (Circa 1960)
  - Item 4: Page 4, 1961; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    (Top) Attending Old Timers' Meeting, Tri-City Local, Rock Island Railroad, 1961. (Bottom) Secretary-Treasurer Collins, myself, and Vice-president Meyers at Meeting.
  - Item 5: Page 5, 1962; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    (Top) Safety Award Dinner, sponsored by the BLF&E/ Center right; Mr. and Mrs. Gerard (General Manager, Great Norther), Mr. and Mrs. Robinson (member of the Presidential Railroad Commission), Mr. and Mrs. Fallon (Vice-president of SUNA). March 1962. (Bottom) Reception for Congressman Gonzalas, (Texas) Washington, 1962. From left to right; Phillips (Assistant Prs. BLF&E), myself, Shattuck Vice-president BLF&E), Mr. X. Congressman Gonzalas, Kennedy (Pres. BRT), Gilbert (Pres. BLF&E), Fallon (Vice-president SUNA).
  - Item 6: Page 6, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    (Top) Myself, Congressman Gonzalas, Kennedy and Gilbert at reception. (Bottom) Newspaper clippings with photo. Left to right: Presidents Neil P. Speirs, Switchmen; Louis J. Wagner, Conductors and Brakemen; H. E. Gilbert, Firemen and Enginemen; Grand Chief Roy E. Davidson, Locomotive Engineers, and President W.P. Kennedy, Trainmen. (circa 1960)
  - Item 7: Page 7, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Secretary of Labor Mitchell, myself, Gilbert and brown at Education Seminar. (circa 1960)
  - Item 8: Page 8, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    (Top) Secretary of Labor addressing Iowa State University students at Seminar. (Bottom) Secretary of Labor Mitchell addressing students. (circa 1960)
  - Item 9: Page 9, 1962; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    (Top) General Chairman Association Meeting, Chicago, 1962. (Bottom) Addressing General Chairmans' Meeting, Chicago, 1962.
  - Item 10: Page 10, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    (Left) Vice-president Van Heck and Myself at meeting. (Right) International Secretary and Treasurer Collins and members of the Finance Insurance Board (SUNA). Seated left to right; Collins, Schrump, standing, Ratsford, Guy. (circa 1960)
  - Item 11: Page 11, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    (Left) Mrs. Eleanor Roosevelt and George Meany, President of the AFL-CIO, at Convention. (Right) Mrs. Roosevelt and Walter Reuther (right), President of the Auto Workers. (circa 1960)
  - Item 12: Page 12, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    (Top) Mrs. Roosevelt, Meany, and Shlitzer, Secretary- Treasurer of AFL-CIO. (Bottom) Mrs. Roosevelt addressing AFL-CIO Convention in Miami Beach. (circa 1960)
  - Item 13: Page 13, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Page 13: SUNA representatives at Convention, Secretary-Treasurer Collins, Vice-president Meyers, and myself. (circa 1960)
  - Item 14: Page 14, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    (Top) SUNA representatives at Convention. (Bottom) Other railway labor representatives. (circa 1960)
  - Item 15: Page 15, 1961; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    (Left, Top) Meeting with Local 263 officers, Roseville, California. (Left, Bottom) Seated left to right; Gonzalas (Local Chairman 145), Pantatoni (Legal Council), Standing, O'Connor (Legal Council), myself, Young (Local Chairman 263), Duffy (Local Chairman 262, Sacramento, Western Pacific). (Right) Addressing local meeting, Sacramento, California, 1961.
  - Item 16: Page 16, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    (Top) Attorney Heiss and Timmerman. (Bottom) SUNA participant for the Presidential Railroad Commission. Left to right; Heiss (attorney), Timmerman (Local Chairman 175, Yuma), myself, Dr. Kaufman (Economist). (circa 1960)
  - Item 17: Page 17, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    President and Vice-presidents of SUNA, 1960. From left to right; Clark, Watson, Van Heck, Fallon, Meyers, Stapp.
  - Item 18: Page 18, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Labor members of the Presidential Railroad Commission, Washington D.C., 1960. From left to right; Zimmerman (Vice-president of BLE), Sites (Vice-president of BRT), Phillips (Assistant president of BLF&E), Holliday (Vice-president of ORC&B), Fallon (Vice-president of SUNA)
  - Item 19: Page 19, 1955-1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    (Top, Right) Sacramento, California, 1955. Seated left to right; Clark (Vice-president), Bruno (President of Local 145), Gonzalas (Local chairman of 145), Shively (Sec.-Tres. Of 145). Standing; McCarthy-(legal counsel SUNA), center; Tunsen, (Top, Left) Nugent addressing dinner. (Bottom, Left) Safety Dinner sponsored by SUNA local 242. (Bottom, Right) Safety meeting, Eugene, Ore., 1958. Standing at right, Nugent (Superintendent of Safety, Southern Pacific).
  - Item 20: Page 20, 1958; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    (Top) Regional Meeting, Sacramento, California, 1958. Left to right; John Burge, mayor of Sacramento, Leo O'Connor (Regional Council of SUNA), Fred Dorius (General chairman, WP), Panatatoni (Regional Council of SUNA). (Bottom) Representative of local lodges in the central California and Nevada areas.
  - Item 21: Page 21, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Buffalo, New York Headquarters of SUNA (circa 1960)
- UTU Founding, Group photograph of 40-Man Committee, 1968; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 2)
  The committee that served as Delegates to the Unification and Constitutional Convention Held at Hot Springs, Arkansas for the purpose of creating the UTU. May 6, 1968. All delegates in photograph are identified (1 photograph)
  - Item 1: Page 1, 1968; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Group Photograph of 40-Man Committee who served as Delegates to the Unification and Constitutional Convention held at Hot Springs, Arkansas, Commencing May 6, 1968. Seated in Front Row: C. E. Wible (BRT) Chairman, PRR-E, N.P. Speirs (SUNA) Int'l President, L.E. Chester (BRT) Assistant to President, C.F. Lane (ORCB) President, H.E. Gilbert (BLFE) President, D.W. Collins (SUNA) Int'l Secretary and Treasurer, J.D. Burke (ORCB) General Chairman, NYC, and M.W. Hampton (BLFE) Assistant President. Standing in Middle Row: J. R. Burge (SUNA) General Chairman, SP (PL), C. F. Traynor (ORCB) General Chairman, N&W (W&LE Dist.), W. H. Callies, (ORCB), General Chairman, C&NW, R. D. Hanon (SUNA), General Chairman Camas Prairie, R. M. Crago (BRT) General Chairman, NYC-S, E. Harris (BRT) General Chairman, Transcontinental Bus System, J. F. Hoffman (BRT) Lodge 74 Local Chairman SP (Pac) Rd., J. F. Kalfas, Jr. (ORCB) General Chairman, B&O, W. D. Huff (ORCB) General Chairman, AT&SF(Coast), C. E. Cook (SUNA) Local Chairman 12, Rock Island, M. A. Ross (BLFE) Vice President, M. H. Nelsen (BLFE) Mbr., Joint Relations Committee, R. R. Bryant (BLFE) General Secretary and Treasurer, W.P. Dunn (BLFE) Mbr., Board of Directors, and D. A. Miller (BLFE) Vice President. Standing in Back Row: L. C. Chisholm (SUNA) Chairman, Int'l Board of Directors, R.C. Flanders (SUNA) Local Chairman 374, C of Ga., T. A. Kunz (BRT) General Chairman, UP-SWD, J. L Green (SUNA) General Chairman. Portland Terminal, P. LaRochelle (BRT) General Chairman, Canadian National East, J. M. Hicks (BRT) General Chairman, L&N, C. W. Zies (SUNA) Local Chairman 164, SP(PL), J. R. Snyder (BRT) State Legislative Representative Georgia, T. P. Lovelace (SUNA) Local Chairman 303, SP(PL), W. G. Stanley (ORCB) General Chairman, Ga. Railroad, J. B. Smith (ORCB) General Chairman, N&W, D. S. Pannell (ORCB) General Chairman, L&N, W. W. Carson (ORCB) Senior Vice President, W. D. Hopkins, (ORCB) General Chairman, D&RGW, P.J. Fontana (BLFE) Mbr., Board of Directors, L. J. Broten (BLFE) Chairman, Board of Directors. A. M. Lampley (BLFE) Vice President & National Legislative Representative was absent from the photo due to illness. G. J. Cahill (BRT) General Chairman, New Haven RR, was also absent from photo due to an urgent matter arising on his property.
- N.P. Speirs with unnamed man at AFL-CIO Convention, New York City, 1963; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 3)
  November 14, 1963 (1 photograph)
  - Item 1: Photo 1, 1963; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Photo of N. P. Speirs and Unnamed man at AFL-CIO Convention, New York City (1963)
- Photographs from U.S. President's Railroad Commission; formation of the UTU; AFL-CIO conventions, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Many of these photographs are found in the scrapbook in folder 1 or in the UTU pamphlets found in collection 6215. Primarily photographs of U.S. President's Railroad Commission and formation of UTU (18 photographs)
  - Item 1: Page 1, 1962; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Reception for Congressman Gonzalas (TX) Washington DC, 1962
  - Item 2: Page 2, 1969; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 4)
    SUNA Headquarters Buffalo, NY 1969
  - Item 3: Page 3, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Neil Speirs
  - Item 4: Page 4, 1965; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Speirs & Unnamed man AFl-CIO Convention San Francisco CA, 1965
  - Item 5: Page 5, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    No caption
  - Item 6: Page 6, 1968; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 4)
    UTO Formation, 1968 Union Presidents & Union Officers. (Standing Left to Right) L. E. Chester (BRT); W. W. Carson (ORC&B), M. W. Hampton (BLF & E), D. W. Collins (SUNA). (Seated Left to Right) Charles Luna (BRT); C. F. Lane (ORC & B ); H. E. Gilbert (BLF&E); N. P. Speirs (SUNA)
  - Item 7: Page 7, 1968; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 4)
    UTO Formation, 1968. (Left to Right) C. Luna; C. F. Lane; H.E. Gilbert; N. P. Speirs
  - Item 8: Page 8, 1968; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 4)
    UTO Formation, 1968
  - Item 9: Page 9, 1968; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Page 10, 1968; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Page 11, 1968; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 4)
    UTO Formation, 1968. Union member vote tallys
  - Item 12: Page 12, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    No Caption
  - Item 13: Page 13, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Page 14, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Page 15, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Page 16, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Page 17, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Page 18, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Group photograph, San Francisco, California, 1952; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Group of unidentified men. San Francisco, California. January, 1952 (1 photograph)
  - Item 1: Page 1, 1952; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Buffalo, NY, SUNA headquarters, black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Speirs and two unidentified men (1 photograph)
- Meeting with Secretary of Labor James Mitchell, Washington, D.C., 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 7)
  October 18, 1960. Also found in scrapbook in folder 1 (1 photograph)
- UTU Merger, 1968; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 8)
  3 photographs of the four union presidents. Charles Luna (BRT), C. F. Lane (ORC&B), H. E. Gilbert (BLF&E), N. P. Speirs (SUNA)
  - Item 1: Page 1, 1967; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 8)
    UTU Merger 1967
  - Item 2: Page 2, 1967; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Page 3, 1967; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Hot Springs, Arkansas. Creation of UTU 1969, black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 9)
  The four union presidents: Luna, Lane, Gilbert, and Speirs (1 photograph) Signing the Agreement to merge four Railroads (sec. Brotherhoods). Presidents of Brotherhood of Brakemen, President of R.R. Firemen, President of Conductors, President of Switchmen. RR. Engineers did not merge with the rest of RR's to form the United Transportation Union.
- Neil Speirs with President Johnson; Secretary Mitchell signs agreement to create President's Railroad Commission, 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  One photograph of Secretary Mitchell, 1960; two photographs of Neil Speirs with President Lyndon B. Johnson and others, 1965 (3 photographs)
  - Item 1: Page 1, 1965; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 10)
    9/30/65 Grandpa Neil Looking at picture, to immediate right of President Lyndon Johnson
  - Item 2: Page 2, 1965; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Grandpa Neil center behind President Johnson 9/30/65
  - Item 3: Page 3, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 10)
    10/18/60 Secretary Mitchell sings the agreement to form a presidential Commission to settle work rules and practices disputes in the railroad industry.
- Neil Speirs Appointment to Railroad Retirement Board, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Neil Speirs Appointment to Railroad Retirement Board Group photo (Left to Right): A. E. Lyons, Mrs. Lyons, Neil Speirs, Mrs. Speirs, Mr. Habermeyer, Mr. Healy (1 photograph)
- Speirs and an unnamed man in front of U.S. Railroad Retirement Board display, 1973; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 12)
  N.P. Speirs and unnamed man in front of U.S Railroad Retirement Board display at International Association of the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees meeting., Detroit, March 29, 1973 (1 photograph)
- Swearing in of Neil Speirs to Railroad Retirement Board, 1969; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Swearing in of Neil Speirs to Railroad Retirement Board, September 26, 1969 (1 photograph)
- Neil Speirs with President Lyndon Johnson and group of men, 1965; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 14)
  9/30/65, Neil Johnson with President Johnson and group of men, (1 photograph)
- U.S. President's Railroad Commission; formation of UTU; SUNA meetings; AFL-CIO conventions, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  (20 photographs)
  - Item 1: Page 1, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 15)
    President & Vice Presidents of SUNA, 1960. (Left to Right) Clark, Watson, Van Heck, Fallon, Meyers, Slapp
  - Item 2: Page 2, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Page 3, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Page 4, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Page 5, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Page 6, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Page 7, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Page 8, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Page 9, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Page 10, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: Page 11, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: Page 12, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: Page 13, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 14: Page 14, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 15: Page 15, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 16: Page 16, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 17: Page 17, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 18: Page 18, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 19: Page 19, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- National Railway Workers' Union of Japan (NRU) visit SUNA headquarters in Buffalo, NY, 1968; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Japanese Nat'l Railroad Rep. visiting SUNA Headquarters in Buffalo, New York See collection 6215 MB, box 1 folder 10, for enameled pins from the NRU (1 photograph), (circa 1968)